2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "I _______________ three movies yesterday, and I loved all of them.";watched;have watched;was watching;watch;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "I _______________ you at the subway station last weekend.";saw;see;was seeing;have seen;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "They _______________ anything to eat yet.";haven't had;didn't have;don't have;are having;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best alternative: "My mother has known him __________ years." ;for;since;to;from;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "Where's Katy? I _______________ her in a while.";haven't seen;didn't see;saw;couldn't see;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "I love my husband. We _______________ married for 30 years now.";have been;are ;were;are being;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "I'm sorry _______________ called you. _______________ very busy lately.";I haven't/I've been;I didn't/I was;I haven't/I am;I didn't/I've been;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative "_______________ to Asia before.";I've never been ;I never been;I didn't go;was never;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "I _______________ this actor several times before. What is his name again?";have seen;saw;had seen;could see;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "_______________ snow falling from the sky?";Have you ever seen;Did you ever see;Were there;There was;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the incorrect alternative: " Have ________________ to Greece? I would love to!";he ever been;you been;they ever traveled ;you ever been;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "We _______________ friends since we _________ small children.";have been/were;are/were;are being/were;were/were;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best alternative: "What a nice restaurant! That was one of the best meals _______________ since I moved here.";I've had;I had;I was having;I will have;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "It _______________ a long time since I talked to her.";has been;have been;was;took;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best answer: "I __________ never __________ to the opera.";have/been;didn't/go;don't/go;haven't/been;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;|Complete the dialogue:
Tessa: "__________ you ever __________ anything valuable?"
John: "No, never."|;Have/lost;Have/been losing;Will/have lost;Had/lost;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best alternative: "Sarah __________ never __________ snails.";has/eaten;didn't/eat;hasn't/eaten;haven't/eaten;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the question: "__________ you ever __________ to Italy?";Have/been;Have/been going;Will/have been;Are/being;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct answer: "I feel sorry for him. He __________ already __________ so many problems.";has/had;will have/had;hasn't/had;didn't/have;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the question: "__________ your cousin ever __________ a job?";Has/had;Have/had;Had/had;Did/have;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "Sally is so tired that she _______________ for more than 12 hours.";has slept;had slept;sleep;sleeps;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the question: "__________ you __________ the news?";Have/heard;Did/heard;Has/heard;Have/hear;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best answer: "Susan __________ already __________ cleaning the house.";has/finished;didn't/finish;has/been finishing;hasn't/finished;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct answer: "Tom _______________ a pie for dinner.";has baked;bake;have baked;haven't baked;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best alternative: "Come on, let's go home. You _______________ too much.";have drunk;hadn't drank;have drank;had drunk;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;|Complete the dialogue:
Ann: "__________ you __________ lunch yet?"
Peter: "Yes, I have."|;Have/had;Do/have;Had/had;Were/having;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "She _______________ skiing yet.";hasn't tried;will have tried;has tried;tried;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best answer: "They __________ just __________ back from Greece.";have/come;have/been coming;have/came;has/came;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the question: "How long __________ he __________ this car?";has/had;have/had;had/had;does/have;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the question: "How long __________ the president __________ in office?";has/been;has/gone;have/been;is/being;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best alternative: "They _______________ each other __________ they were at school.";have known/since;have known/for;know/since;knew/for;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "He can't play because he _______________ his homework yet.";hasn't done;haven't done;will have done;hasn't made;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "They __________ already __________ the same question over and over again.";have/asked;have/done;didn't/ask;haven't/asked;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "Oh, no! She __________ just __________ the wrong bus!";has/caught;did/catch;has/catch;didn't/catch;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "__________ you ever __________ to call the police for any reason?";Have/had;Did/have;Had/had;Did/had;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the question: "__________ you ever __________ an article for a magazine?";Have/written;Did/write;Did/wrote;Have/wrote;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the question: "__________ you ever __________ a horse at the beach?";Have/ridden;Have/rode;Did/ride;Have/ride;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "I _______________ interesting people since I _______________ here.";have met/moved;meet/moved;met/have moved;meet/have moved;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;|Complete the dialogue:
Susan: "Are the journalists here?"
Joshua: "They __________ just __________."|;have/arrived;had/arrived;were/arrived;did/arrive;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Fill in the gap with the correct alternative: "She _______________ abroad for 2 years during university.";has lived;lived;was living;haven't lived;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "I have a cousin who _______________ abroad.";has never been;never was;never went;had been ;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "They _______________ the project last month.";finished;have finished;had finished;have to finish;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "I _______________ Mathematics for 20 years. Now, I am retired.";have taught;taught;was teaching;have been teaching;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "I _______________ to 7 different countries in my life.";have been;went;was;travelled;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "He is the only one who _______________.";hasn't arrived yet;doesn't arrive yet;didn't arrive yet;haven't arrived yet;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best alternative: "I _______________ a lot since I started this course.";have learned;am learning;learned;was learning;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "The winner of the contest _______________ yet.";hasn't been announced;has been announced;wasn't announced;didn't announce;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "This city _______________ a lot since we moved here.";has changed;changed;changes;have changed;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the question: "How many books _______________ during his career?";has he written;he wrote;does he write;he has written;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the question: "Do you know what happened to Dan? I _______________ him since Monday.";haven't seen;didn't see;don't see;hasn't seen;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "_______________ you his new car yet?";Has he shown;Did he show;He has shown;He showed;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;|Complete the dialogue:
Robert: "_______________ to Africa?"
Christian: "No, _______________ abroad."|;Have you ever been/I've never been;Did you ever go/I never went;Did you ever be/I was never;You've ever been/I've never been;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "I'm not hungry, _______________ just __________ breakfast.";I've/had;I/having;I've/have;I/have;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "My daughter _______________ a lot of friends since we moved to France.";has made;made;is making;didn't make;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "The car sales business is more difficult than I thought. I _______________ any car yet.";haven't sold;didn't sell;have sold;won't sell;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;|Complete the dialogue:
Catherine: "Would you like a slice of pizza?"
Paul: "No, thanks. _______________ dinner."|;I've already had;I have;I can have ;I would have;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the question: "_______________ your honeymoon destination yet?";Have you chosen;Did you choose;Could you choose;Will you choose;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "Robert __________ a lifeguard since he was twenty-one years old.";has been;is being;is;was;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "My nephew was born yesterday, but _______________ him yet.";I haven't visited;I didn't visit;I didn't go visit;I visited;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "My husband and I __________ just __________ a house in the hills.";have/bought;have/buy;did/buy;has/bought;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "I've just __________ the best chocolate cake in the world.";eaten;ate;eat;eating;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "This is the best book I've _______________.";ever read;just read;about to read;always read;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "Switzerland is the most beautiful country _______________.";I've ever been to;I've just been to;I went;I was;;JM
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct answer: "The sea level _______________ over the past few years.";has risen;rose;is rising;will rise;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best answer: "The temperature in the South _______________ over the last few days.";has dropped;drops;dropped;will drop;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "I _______________ a kite since I was a child.";haven't flown;didn't fly;don't fly;won't fly;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best alternative: "John _______________ several different mountains since he was 15.";has climbed;will have climbed;climbs;is climbing;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Fill in the gap with the correct answer: "Sarah _______________ several championships over the last years";has won;wins;won;is winning;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Fill in the gap with the best answer: "Matt _______________ chess for years.";has played;plays;played;is playing;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Fill in the gap with the correct alternative: "We _______________ to Africa twice over the last couple of years.";have been;went;will go;are going to;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Fill in the gap with the best alternative: "I _______________ in a tent quite a few times since I moved here.";have slept;slept;didn't sleep;am sleeping;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "I __________ already __________ quite a few apple pies since I learned how to cook.";have/made;didn't/make;will have/made;am/making;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct answer: "I _______________ many pictures on the internet since I started using the computer.";have posted;posted;didn't post;am posting;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best answer: "In all my life I __________ never __________ my car.";have/crashed;didn't/crash;haven't/crashed;don't/never;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "She __________ never __________ herself while preparing dinner.";has/cut;didn't/never;hasn't/cut;doesn't/cut;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best alternative: "People _______________ more interested in learning languages over the past few years.";have been;are;aren't;are being;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Fill in the gap with the correct answer: "John _______________ his passport many times over the years.";has lost;didn't lose;lost;is losing;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Fill in the gap with the best answer: "Sam _______________ him many letters since he left the country.";has written;wrote;didn't write;is writing;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Fill in the gap with the correct alternative: "They _______________ terrible holidays for the past few years.";have had;didn't have;had;are having;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Fill in the gap with the best alternative: "Wait a second, I _______________ it yet.";haven't finished;didn't finish;finished;have finished;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "Sally _______________ here since ten o'clock.";has been;is;is being;was;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the question: "__________ you ever __________ any money in the street?" ;Have/found;Will/have found;Will/be finding;Should/find;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct answer: "I __________ already __________ someone who won the lottery.";have/met;didn't/meet;won't/have met;wouldn't/meet;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best answer: "I _______________ quite a few important tests over the past few years.";have failed;failed;didn't fail;am failing;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "Sam _______________ several doctors over the past few weeks.";has seen;didn't see;saw;is seeing;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best alternative: "Alex _______________ interested in cinema since he was a child.";has been;was;is;will be;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Fill in the gap with the correct answer: "They __________ already __________ to Australia three times.";have/been;didn't/go;did/go;were/been;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Fill in the gap with the best answer: "I _______________ my job for 2 years now.";have had;didn't have;had;am having;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Fill in the gap with the correct alternative: "Sam _______________ a job yet.";hasn't found;has found;found;is going to find;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Fill in the gap with the best alternative: "Sarah __________ never __________ the Star Wars movie.";has/seen;hasn't/seen;didn't/see;doesn't/see;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "Andrew _______________ a lot since last December.";has learned;learned;learns;didn't learn;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the question: "How long __________ you __________ Ted?";have/known;do/know;are/knowing;don't/know;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct answer: "Tessa started writing a new article but she _______________ it yet.";hasn't finished;didn't finish;doesn't finish;has finished;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best answer: "This band _______________ great success since the early 90s.";has had;had;has;didn't have;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct alternative: "Several animal species _______________ extinct over the last few years.";have become;became;will become;become;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best alternative: "The children must be hungry. They _______________ anything since breakfast.";haven't eaten;ate;aren't eating;have eaten;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the sentence: "The Smiths __________ always __________ about the environment. They recycle everything!" ;have/worried;didn't/worry;don't/worry;haven't/worried;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Complete the question: "__________ you always __________ this necklace? I don't remember it.";Have/had;Do/have;Are/having;Had/had;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the correct answer: "Allan must be tired. He _______________ out shopping since early in the morning.";has been;was;is;has been;;JG
2;Intermediate;Present perfect;Choose the best answer: "__________ you __________ into a new apartment?";Have/moved;Has/moved;Did/moved;Have/move;;JG
